<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Enigmelo Blog</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Enigmelo Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 16:36:04 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>SSH Keystroke Obfuscation Bypass</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/ssh-obfuscation-bypass/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 16:36:04 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/ssh-obfuscation-bypass/</guid>
      <description>Introduction OpenSSH version 9.5 introduced measures to mitigate a keystroke timing attack via traffic analysis. The patch involved adding keystroke timing obfuscation to the SSH client. As per the release notes, this feature “attempts to hide inter-keystroke timings by sending interactive traffic at fixed intervals (default: every 20ms) when there is only a small amount of data being sent”. Additionally, fake chaff packets are sent after the last real keystroke, significantly complicating traffic analysis by shrouding the real keystrokes in a stream of impostors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SSHniff</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/sshniff/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/sshniff/</guid>
      <description>SSHniff: An SSH Metadata Analyser As part of my final-year bachelor research project, I took a stab at determining how feasible a metadata-based attack on the SSH protocol is nowadays. This type of attack was first introduced in 2001, in a paper called &amp;ldquo;Timing Analysis of Keystrokes and Timing Attacks on SSH&amp;rdquo;. It is based on the fact that interactive SSH sessions leak significant metadata. Keystrokes, while encrypted, are sent to and echoed by the server individually.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HTB Business CTF - Swarm Writeup</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/swarm/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 18:18:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/swarm/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This is a writeup for my 2024 Hack The Box Business CTF FullPwn Machine, Swarm. While I was not initially planning on creating a dedicated writeup for the machine, it was brought to my attention that many players regarded the privilege escalation as ungodly. As such, I felt a responsibility to provide the traumatised players with a thorough explanation for my creation.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/about/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m Philip, aka melo, and I do a little coding. This blog&amp;rsquo;s purpose is to host any disclosures and/or security research conducted by me, or other stuff that I feel worthy of sharing with the world. I&amp;rsquo;m currently working as a cybersecurity researcher at the UK AI Safety Institute (AISI).&#xA;You can also find me here:&#xA;GitHub: https://github.com/CrzPhil LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/philipgiavridis Twitter: https://twitter.com/enigmelo HackTheBox: https://app.hackthebox.com/profile/458049 Contact I occasionally check this inbox: enigmelo86@gmail.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
